[Music]
whenever i meet a person i often notice
their eyes
i particularly love those little
wrinkles that form around them when they
smile i enjoy when someone shares a
topic they're passionate about their
face has a way of lighting up and the
vibrancy is in their voice
when someone is kind they shine a light
that makes others feel as if the world
is a little better than a minute before
[Music]
so
i know what it is to have no self-esteem
and when i was able to finally crawl out
of that hole and find that stability in
regards to how i see myself i was
surprised that being comfortable wasn't
necessarily being confident in how i
looked it was simply being at peace with
who i was
to give a very silly example i'm told
quite often online that i have an
unfortunately large nose it comes with
the territory of being someone on the
internet
these comments are often attempting to
make me feel self-conscious but
i'm happy to say it doesn't because it
relies on me agreeing with their
perception and internalizing it
and that is where my power lies and
yours does too
indeed words become real only if you
believe they are
[Music]
when you get to that place it's
incredible to feel that freedom and all
time spent critiquing my own or others
external selves seems like a waste of
potential
my life minutes could be used in so many
other wondrous ways
i asked all of you what made a person
beautiful and without fail i got the
words of compassion and honesty
and that's interesting because in a way
those are some of the easiest things to
be
it may be hard at the very start when we
have layers of fear and hurt in our way
but once those walls come down we're
free
and just like that we become something
so beautiful
it cannot be described through a
physical representation
we can spend the rest of time debating
physical beauty but i would really like
to spend that time wondering how i can
cultivate a beauty that lasts forever
i think that's a far more interesting
question
[Music]
i have been working on this little bunny
rabbit all morning
and
i have to say it has filled me with so
much joy i
am always surprised by the little things
that bring me
little moments of just happiness
throughout the day
and this is one of them i think getting
creative and making something um you
know that isn't necessarily very
complicated or anything but just
something that brings you joy it's so
beautiful and i think so important on a
daily basis you know if it's possible
depending on the person
you know there are different things that
may bring you joy
i know for a lot of people it's coffee
for some people it may be their pets you
know
laying in bed after a long day of work
cupcakes and cookies
for me today
what brings me joy
is painting a little bunny with a
mushroom cap
because it's so simple
but something about it
just making my day
so
sometimes it's just simplest most
darling little things
that make all the difference
[Music]
you